Guide to the Center for International Studies records, 1960-1983.
Center for International Studies records
- Series IX. Education Documents
  - Preliminary Report to HEW on the Status of Demographic Training in the United States, May 15, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - "Problem or Topic-Oriented Programs in International Studies at the Graduate Level", 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Assorted Notices on Education, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - International Interaction: Bulletin of the International Education project, February 1975 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - "Program for Strengthening the International Dimensions of General Education at the Undergraduate Level" (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Papers Concerned with Continuing Support for International Education, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "Statement Before the Subcommittee on Labor, Health, Education, and Welfare, House Committee on Appropriations" by W. Donald Cooke, Acting Provost and Vice President for Research, Cornell University, May 14, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Problem or Topic-Oriented Programs in International Studies at the Graduate Level, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Office of Education Proposed Rules for Modern Foreign Languages and Area Studies, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Draft of Environmental Education Act: Handbook on Preparing Proposals, October 1971 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Invitation for Proposals for Assistance to New Kinds of Graduate Programs in International Studies, March 1, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Workshop on the Role of the Council for Scientific and Industrial Research in Determining Science Policy and Research Priorities, October 21, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Assorted Papers on Science Policy, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Various Papers Concerning CIS and Science and Technology Studies, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Announcement and Guidelines for Centers for Modern Foreign Language and Area Studies (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Title IX of Educational Amendments of 1972, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Assorted Articles on International Education (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - "International Education Act-Another Call to Action", October 1, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Series X. International Involvement and Affairs
  - International Law
    - Various Papers Associated with International Law Program, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence Between the Law School and CIS About Supplementing the Law Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Outline for a Law School Seminar on Problems of War and Peace (and related discussion), January-March 1976 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence about the Peace Studies and International Law Programs, January-May 1976 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Papers on the International Legal Studies Program Plans and Financing for 1975-1976 and 1976-1977, 1975-1976 and 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Budget Request, International Legal Studies Program, 1976-1977, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - International Legal Studies, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Assorted Flyers for International Law and Peace Organizations, 1960-1970 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Reports on the World Law Fund, September 1971-September 1972 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Assorted International Law Papers, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Proposals to the General Electric Foundation from the International Legal Studies Program, February 1974 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Letters About Applicants for Positions in CIS International Law, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Institute of European Studies
    - The Institute of European Studies, "A New Plan for Affiliation", March 15, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Institute of European Studies Papers, October 1973 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - The Institute of European Studies: Announcements, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Institute of European Studies, mid 1970s (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - World Food
    - "Trends in World Food Supply and Demand Balance," by Lyle P. Schertz, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Assorted World Food Papers, May-August 1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - World Food-Publicity, Fall 1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - World Food: Directory Requests, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - World Food: Undergraduate Course Offering, Spring 1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Directory of International Food Studies at Cornell University (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - World Food Professor Profiles (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - World Food Faculty Seminar, Fall 1975 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - "The Great World Crisis I," by Geoffrey Barraclough (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - World Food: General, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - International Nutrition Projects, Brochures, and Releases, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - International Nutrition Faculty Papers, 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Proposals: International Nutrition (Internal, not yet sent out), Spring 1973 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - International Nutrition Projects, SubSahara Famine, July 1973 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - "Program on International Nutrition and Development Policy" (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Proposal for Support Under the Agency for International Development Institutional Grants Program by Program of International Nutrition and Development, October 30, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - "World Food: A Directory of Education: Resources at Cornell University" (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Vietnam and Indochina
    - Correspondence about Indochina with the International Assembly of Christians, September 1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Papers from the International Commission of Enquiry in U.S. Crimes in Indochina; in Copenhagen, October 10-16, 1972, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - News Release from Bureau of Public Affairs Concerning Documentation of Vietnam Agreement, January 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - "The Air War and Syracuse University," by Fred Branfman, February 13, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - "Statement on Military Research Conducted by the Syracuse University Research Corporation", February 23, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Documents Related to the International Conference for the Implementation of the Paris Agreement on Vietnam", March-April 1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Papers Relating to Syracuse University and Vietnam, 1973, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - "The United States Air Force in Korea," by Robert Frank Futrell, 1950-1953 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - "World Politics," Vol. XV, April 1963 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - "American Aircraft Systematically Attack Dams and Dikes in the D.R.V.N.", 1968 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Newspapers on the Use of Forest Fires in Vietnam, Late 1960s (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - "Population Defenses: Have We Been All Through It Before?" by George H. Quester, Reprinted from Public Policy, Volume XVIII, Fall 1970 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - "Scientists and the Politics of Technology," by Frank von Hippel and Joel Pumack, Summer 1971 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - "Indochina", 1971 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Ad Hoc Military Buildup Committee: Overall Summary, April 15, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Indochina Chronicle and Related Resources, April 1972 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Reports on the Wars in Indochina, May 3-9, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - A Staff Report Prepared for the Use of the Subcommittee on U.S. Security Agreements and Commitments: Abroad of the Committee on Foreign Relations, United States Senate, May 8, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - "The Indochina War: Perspectives and Recent Events", May 12, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - "The Cratering of Indochina," by Arthur H. Westing and E.W. Pfeiffer from "Scientific American," Volume 226, May 1972 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Criticism of U.S.'s Actions Against North and South Vietnam, May 1972 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - "Heroin Traffic in Southeast Asia," "The Washington Post", June 2, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - "Laotian Civilian War Casualties in the Plain of Jars," Submitted to "Science", June 1972 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Harper's Magazine, June 1972 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Indochina War Fact Sheet, Delivered to Professor Raphael Littaner by Tucson Peace Center, July 1972 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - "The Cambodian Liberation Forces," by Laura Summer, Serge Thien, Chris Jenkins, and Christine Keller, July 1, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Assorted Papers on Foreign Policy with Vietnam, Spring 1972 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - "Intellectual Digest", November 1972 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - "New Priorities", Winter 1972 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - "The Climate of VN", 1972 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Armament Data Sheets, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Newspaper Articles About Nixon's Foreign Policy, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Assorted Newspaper Articles on Vietnam, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Supplement to "Air War: The Third Indochina War", Spring 1972 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Assorted Articles About the War in Indochina, 1972-1973, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Assorted Papers Related to Vietnam, 1972-1973, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Review of "Pluses and Minuses of Air War in 'Nam", February 28, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - International Day of Concern Poster, September 23, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Papers on Political Prisoners Detained by Republic of Vietnam, June-July 1973 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Coalition to Free South Vietnamese Political Prisoners Papers, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - "Study of Terror" Documents on Political Imprisonment, Torture, and Repression in South Vietnam", 1973 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - "Thieu's Political Prisoners," by Jean-Pierre Debris and Andrea Menras, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Newspaper Articles Discussing Vietnam and Cambodia, 1970s (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Assorted Articles Relating to Indochina, 1970s (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Article on Remote War in Indochina (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Assorted Notes and Articles on Air War (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - "No Peace/No Honor-American Responsibility for Torture of Saigon Prisoners" (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Assorted Graphics Concerning North and South Vietnam (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - First Draft: "The Laws of Warfare and the Air War in Southeast Asia," by Arthur W. Rovine, September 1971 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - "Meeting Whose Need," by Vincent Pollard, from the Far Eastern Economic Review, Volume 73 No. 39, November 17, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - "Land War," from Environment, Volume 13 No.9, November 1971 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - "The Death Harvesters," by Michael Malloy, from "Far Eastern Economic Review", January 29, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - "Chapter 11: The Air War and International Law," latest draft, February 12, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Neil Sheehan's Preface from "The Air War in Indochina," March 13, 1972, March 13, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - "Report on the International Commission of Enquiry into US Crimes in Indochina," by Hans-Goran Franck, March 1972, March 1972 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - First Proof for "Combat by Proxy" Article in "Harper's Magazine", April 12, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - "Vietnam and the War Powers Crisis," An Address by Senator Jacob K. Javits, May 20, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - "Air Power in Indochina: Doublethink 1972," by Raphael Littauer, August 26, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Correspondence Mainly Related to Raphael Littauer, August 1972 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - "Beacon Press", Fall 1972 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - 2nd International Assembly of Christians in Solidarity with the Vietnamese, Laotion, and Cambodian Peoples, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - "The Bombing of North Vietnam: Tip of the Iceberg," by Raphael Littauer (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - "The American Way of Bombing" (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Assorted Papers on the War with Indochina (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Notes About the State of Indochina (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - "Canada in Vietnam," "Bias": Volume 2 Number 1 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Reference cards for people in dialogue about Indochina (Box 11)
    - "North Vietnam against U.S. air force", 1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - "American Aircraft Systematically Attack Dams and Dikes in D.R.V.N., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Laos Statistics, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Assorted Articles and Notes on Vietnam, 1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Tonnage, 1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Statistics about Vietnam and Indochina, 1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Troop Levels, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - "Attack Carrier: The Constellation Papers", September 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - "Saturday Review," Vol. LIV, No.46, November 13, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Information Leaked by Fred Hoffman, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Articles about U.S. Missiles, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - "The Nixon Administration in Indochina," by Gabriel Kolko, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Assorted Newspaper Articles about Vietnam, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Articles and Papers About Laos, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Articles about North Vietnam, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Papers and Articles on Cambodia, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Assorted Newspaper Articles on Indochina, 1970s, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - VNAF, Early 1970s (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - A/C Losses, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Casualties, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Graphics about Vietnam and Indochina (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - A/C Inventory (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Assorted Articles and Papers about Indochina (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Assorted Papers about Vietnam and Indochina (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Assorted News Releases and Related Papers (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Abstracts and Summaries *study Reading), Literature Numerical Listings (Box 12)
    - Interview and Trip Reports (Box 12)
    - Status Reports (Box 12)
    - Bibliographies and Surveys Concerning US War with Indochina (Box 12)
    - Binder of Documents About the Air War in Indochina, 1970s (Box 12)
    - Vietnam Policy Papers, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Vietnam Policy Newspaper Articles, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Southeast Asia Development Advising Group conference audio reels (Box 11)
    Reels appear to be from a conference with support from the Rockefeller Foundation and the United States Agency for International Development. A number of individuals from Southeast Asian countries are in attendance and are introduced by the emcee on side 1 of the first reel.
    - Reel 1/2, tr-9954 (Box 11)
      Side 1: Harry Oshima. Side 2: Warren Ilchman
    - Reel 3/4, tr-9955 (Box 11)
      Side 1: Discussion, Pol and Admin, Montgomery, Napitupulu. Side 2: Napitupulu, Pradoldej, Kaminruddin, Wong, Patten.
    - Reel 5/6, tr-9956 (Box 11)
      Side 1: Patten, Sibero, Banskota. Side 2: Banskota, Vichit, Bhalla, Chira.
    - Reel 7/8, tr-9957 (Box 11)
      Side 1: Chira, Chang, Ayub. Side 2: Ayub, Esman, Bhalla.
    - Reel 9/10, tr-9958 (Box 11)
      Side 1: Locsin, Osatananda, Pham, Alfonso. Side 2: Alfonso, Discussion, Final Session
    - Reel 11, tr-9959 (Box 11)
      Side 1: Final Session, Multiple Cropping, End. Side 2: Blank
    - Assorted Papers on the Air War in Indochina (Book and Topic), 1972 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Assorted Documents Concerning "The Air War in Indochina", 1972 (Box 18, Folder 96)
  - China and Japan
    - "Understanding China: An Assessment of American Scholarly Resources," 1971, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Assorted Papers Concerning Programs Dealing with China and Japan, 1974-1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - China Program, February 1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - "Peking Review", October 6, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper Articles About China and US Education, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - China Japan Deans Council, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence Concerning Work with China, July 1979 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - "Building New Educational Relationships Between the University of Minnesota and Institutes of Higher Education in the People's Republic of China"; from a trip September 1-21, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - "Agriculture in the Four Modernizations," by Thomas B. Wiens, from Cornell Workshop on Agricultural and Rural Development in the People's Republic of China, May 17-19, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - List of Universities in People's Republic of China, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - China Exchange, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - China Conference, May 17-May 19, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Papers and Correspondence Concerning CIS Trip to China, 1980, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - "China Exchange News," Volume 8, Number 1 and 2, February and April 1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - "An Introduction to Education in the People's Republic of China and US-China Educational Exchanges", 1980 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Papers for CIS Trip to China, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Delegate Resumes and Papers for Visit to China, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence about Chinese and American Scholars Visiting Each Other's Universities, July-October 1981 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Information About CIS Trip to China, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Papers About the Philippines Project, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report of the Cornell Philippines Project, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Philippines - Staff/Faculty Appts. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Philippines - Gen. Corres. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Funds for CIS Philippines Project (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - South Asia Program Papers and Correspondence, 1966-1976 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Minutes of South Asia Program Meeting Held on April 13, 1967, April 13, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Minutes of Grant Allocation and South Asia Studies Meeting, April 27, 1967, April 27, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - "Two Strategies of Institutional Development in Latin America", October 12, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - "On Building the Behavioral Sciences in Peru", September 15, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - CIS Peruvian Project, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - CIS Peru Project Papers, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Peru Project Financing (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - "Preliminary Report of US Survey Team on Projected Korea", August 20, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Various Papers Concerning Soviet Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Language and Area Program, Title VI: USSR and Eastern Europe, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Yugoslav Project, 1969-1976 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - "The Administration of Research and Institutional Development: Lessons from our Peruvian Program", January 1970 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - South Asia Program: James W. Gair, Dr., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Papers Concerning Cornell's Presence in Ghana, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Papers on Cornell's Presence in Costa Rica, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - "Inter-American Program in Linguistics and Language Teaching (PILEO)", June 9, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence Concerning Jack-Fisher and the American-Yugoslav Project, 1964-1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Yugoslav Project General, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Documents Concerning an American-Yugoslav Project Book, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Sources of Program Expenditure for American-Yugoslav Project (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Papers on the Cornell-Turin International Centre Program, February-March 1968 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Synthesis of the Principal Conclusions of the Workshop on Implementation of Self-managed Systems in the Third World, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Papers on the Cornell-Turin International Centre Program, February-March 1968 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Summary Budget for Selected Projects on Science and Technology Policy for Developing Nations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - International Studies for Engineers, October 4, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Philippines Project, October 12, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - China Program, 1967-1978 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Report and Request of the Cornell China Program to the Ford Foundation, by David Mazingo, February 22, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Program on Policies Science and Technology in Developing Nations (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - CIS-Symposium on South Africa (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Environmental Studies (W.Lynn), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Peasant Study - Lansberger, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Tropical Soils Research, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Environ. Financial, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Philippines Project, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Latin Amer. Linguistics, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Yugoslavia Project, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Cenis Sub comt. - Overseas ops., 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - South Asia Comt., 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - "The American-Yugoslav Project for Joint Research and Training in Regional Planning", May 1965 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Comparative Labor Relations Research: United States and Japan; Join Research Proposal, October 15, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - "Paucartambo, Pasco, Peru: Whence...Whither," by David H. Andrews et al., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Cornell-Sydney Radio-Astron., February 1966 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - SCH. of Nutrition- Ghana, Puerto Rico, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - China-Taiwan-Galenson, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - CURW-Brazil, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - ILR-Turin Project, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Comt. Overseas Ops, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - "A Proposal by the Division of Biological Sciences of Cornell University and the Academic Unit of Basic Biological Sciences of the Universidad del Valle", March 20, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Law School-India, August 1968 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Latin Amer. Program (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - "The University of the West Indies (at Trinidad) and the Teaching of Management" (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Liberia Project, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Turkey Project, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - London-Cornell Project: Seminars, Chinese Societies 1965 Seminars (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - London-Cornell Project: Seminars, China 1966 Seminars (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Information on Cornell Study Abroad Programs, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Papers on Foreign Currencies, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - London-Cornell Project Tenth Annual Report tot he Carnegie Corporation of New York Covering the Fiscal and Academic Year, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Papers and Documents on Arms and Related Topics, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - International Studies Plans and Papers, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "A Project to Develop and Appraise Interpretive Techniques for Data Acquisition from Aerial Photographs to Service and Evaluate Programs in Developing Countries," Prepared by Center for Aerial Photographic Studies, Cornell University (and Related Papers), 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - "Social Unrest, Social Class, and Quebec's Bureaucratic Revolution," by Hubert Guindon, from "Canadian Society: Sociological Perspectives", 1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 3, "Historical Setting," in "Area Handbook for Malaysia", 1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Assorted Papers for Presentations on Technical Assistance in Public Administration, 1970s (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Overseas Foreign Language and Area Studies Programs, Faculty Research and Study Program, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Assorted Documents Pertaining to Cornell Programs on International Issues, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on International Education Policy, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - International Law Outline for Concerns and Improvements, July 17, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - International Law Proposal Concerning Student Oriented Program Activities and the Comparative Study of Environmental Laws (1972-1977), December 1971 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Papers on a Program for International Nutrition, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - International Law Outline for Concerns and Improvements, July 17, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Papers Concerning Ford Foundation Grant for International Nutrition, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - September 11, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 82)